

ASHLEY W O H L R A B

BUSINESS STUDENT

CONTACT

845 405 1219 ASHLEY.WOHLRAB1@MARIST.EDU ASHLEYW706.GITHUB.IO

PROFILE

A rising senior at Marist College, studying Business Administration, Human Resources, and Data Science and Analytics. Relevant leadership experience as well as experience in fast food and customer service. Truly passionate about helping others and making the world a better place for all.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CREW TRAINER

MODENA TRAVEL PLAZA | JUN 2015 - PRESENT

- Maintained high standards of customer service during highvolume, fast-paced operations
- Cross-trained and coordinated scheduling with team members to ensure seamless service
- Communicated clearly and positively with coworkers and management

INTERVIEWER

MARIST INSTITUTE FOR PUBLIC OPINION | JUN 2019 - PRESENT

• Worked as an interviewer at a survey research center where my main responsibility was to make calls and execute standardized surveys to the public for polling purposes.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, MAJOR IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

MARIST COLLEGE | 2016 - 2020

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Event Planning
- Strong Leadership and delegation skills
- Excellent time management
- Experience with Python, HTML, and CSS.
- Organization Skills
- Excellent Customer Service Skillset
- Willingness to Learn new skills
- Loyal, Devoted, and Driven to Succeed

NOTABLE AFFILIATIONS

SOCIETY OF HUMAN RESOURCES MANAGEMENT MEMBER OF MARIST COLLEGE CHAPTER OCT 2018 - PRESENT

KAPPA KAPPA PSI SECRETARY AND SERVICE CHAIR SPRING 2018 - FALL 2018

NATIONAL SOCIETY FOR LEADERSHIP AND SUCCESS MEMBER OF MARIST COLLEGE CHAPTER APR 2017 - PRESENT

MID HUDSON CHILDREN'S MUSEUM VOLUNTEER JUN 2019 - PRESENT